http://www.copsplus.com/privacy.php

Privacy Notice
CopsPlus.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting CopsPlus.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does CopsPlus.com Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at CopsPlus.com. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way.  You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store, and communicating with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies", and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses CopsPlus.com. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at CopsPlus.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.
Email Communications: To help us make emails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open email from CopsPlus.com if your computer supports such capabilities.
What About Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of CopsPlus.com's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Does CopsPlus.com Share the Information It Receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit CopsPlus.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our
Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of New York. If you have any concern about privacy at CopsPlus.com, please contact us and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly.
CloseoutsHolstersDuty HolstersTactical HolstersBelt HolstersPancake HolstersPaddle HolstersInside-the-Pant HolstersShoulder HolstersFanny Packs & PursesAnkle HolstersHolster AccessoriesBeltsDuty BeltsGarrison BeltsDress & Sport BeltsBelt KeepersDuty GearBaton HoldersChemical Spray CarriersFlashlight HoldersGlove PouchesHandcuff CasesKey HoldersMagazine PouchesRadio & Pager HoldersRadio AccessoriesSpeedloadersPolice K9 GearBadge WalletsPolice BadgesStar BadgesBadges with EaglesBadges without EaglesOval BadgesFire BadgesCanadian BadgesMini Police BadgesRestraintsHandcuffsLeg & Waist ChainsHandcuff KeysFlashlightsStandard FlashlightsRechargeable FlashlightsWeapon LightsPen & Micro LightsBatteries & AccessoriesPolice BatonsExpandable BatonsFixed Length BatonsTraining BatonsRadios and AccessoriesRadio HeadsetsMegaphonesFootwearMens Boots & ShoesWomens Boots & ShoesApparel and UniformsBody ArmorPants and ShortsShirtsUnder GearHeadgearJackets and OuterwearProtective GlovesSunglassesWatches and JewelryMorale PatchesPepper SprayPolice Duty SprayPersonal Pepper SprayInert Training SprayKnivesAutomatic KnivesFolding KnivesFixed Blade KnivesMulti-ToolsTactical PensTraining KnivesSheathsEquipment BagsPolice Equipment BagsBackpacks & HydrationLong Gun Carry BagsPistol CasesMetal DetectorsHandheld DetectorsWalkthrough DetectorsTactical-MilitaryTactical HolstersTactical BeltsTactical PouchesTactical VestsTactical AccessoriesTactical LightsTactical GlovesTactical KnivesTactical Bags & PacksTactical Entry ToolsGun AccessoriesGun AmmoGun SlingsGun CleaningGun Locks & SafesGun Grips & AccessoriesOpticsNight Vision OpticsSpotting & Gun ScopesBinocularsVehicle EquipmentClipboards & OrganizersTraining and SafetyTraining SuppliesAirsoft Guns & AccessoriesSafety Glasses & GogglesHearing ProtectionPPE GearGas MasksPolice Riot GearTraffic SafetyInvestigationsFingerprintsEvidence GatheringDrug IdentificationFire and RescueFirefighter Turnout GearFire and Rescue LightsRescue ToolsEMT GearFree Widgets For Your WebsiteOfficers Lost RemembranceClick to DownloadLicense Plate Hit CounterClick to DownloadCustomer ServiceContact UsOrder StatusReturns & ExchangesLow Price GuaranteeSecure ShoppingYour PrivacyConditionsSite MapTop CategoriesDuty HolstersBelt HolstersShoulder HolstersTactical ApparelBoots & ShoesProtective GlovesHandcuffsPolice Equipment BagsTop BrandsGalco HolstersSafariland Duty HolstersBianchi Duty GearBlackhawk Tactical Gear5.11 Tactical GearUncle Mikes Police GearASP BatonsBenchmade KnivesPopular Gun Fits1911 HolstersBeretta HolstersGlock HolstersH&K USP HolstersRuger HolstersS&W HolstersSig HolstersSERPA HolstersCustomer Service: (800) 330-64223801 23rd Avenue, #407 Astoria, NY 11105©2002-2020 CopsPlus.com: Privacy Notice
Inova T4 850 Lumen Rechargeable LED Tactical FlashlightOnly $97.00 - Save 32%58 Remain: BUY NOW
